<dataset>
<post>
  <title>Goodbay Blogger, Hallo Flogger</title>
  <date>2012-03-09</date>
  <content>
    <heading1>Why goodbay blogger.com ?</heading1>
    <paragraph>

Have you tried to make a backup from blogger.com ? I've tried in February 2012 and the
result was not pleasent. Mainly because of two resoan, first (and more importantly)the
output was not in clear format(not readable by human). second was not  important.

So, I've decide to build my own blog and first future will be ability to export blog
in readable format. For example all texts could appear as you are seeing it now! :-)

    </paragraph>
    <heading1>Why hallo flogger ?</heading1>
    <paragraph>

Honestly I didn't search enought to find another Blogger like websites in the web, in-
stead I've thought about what cool feature a bolg could have for programmers and read-
ers ?
Here is my list for readers :

  * ability to download hole blog with one click and see texts in their own machines.
  * ability to select a theme for reading, for example plain text, xml, html, etc.
  * not seeing any ads or distraction from others existing things in the web.

Here is my list for programmers :

  * ability to have hole blog under source version controls (e.g. svn) and by each co-
    mmit, blog update automatically.
  * ability to post to the web from command line console (not using any web browser).
  * working with open source, clean code wrritten blog software ...

    <paragraph>
    <heading2>What next ?</heading2>
    <paragraph>

Let's start with simplest available solution today, as we speak github.com is avaiable
for hosting the source code for open source projects. heroku.com is avaiable for host-
ing project with single free node. thoughtworks.com is available for offering neat op-
en source tools (e.g. cruisecontrol.rb).

I am thinking to make a project(flogger) in github.com and by help of thoughtworks to-
ols, build a build pipeline (for automate deployment) and labblah687.heroku.com would
be my future blog web address.

let's do that ;-)
    <paragraph>

  </content>
</post>
